Due to the high volume of calls, we're experiencing a higher-than-usual backlog.

We appreciate your patience. In the meantime, please refer to our [Resource Directory](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/resources), [Special Education Legal Library](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/training-portal/special-education-resources/home/), or [Insurance Portal](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/insurance-portal-toc/) as needed on our website while you're waiting

[

](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/gala)[MORE INFO](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/give)

[

](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/)

Privacy Policy
==============

This privacy policy sets out how WashingtonAutismAdvocacy.org uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. WashingtonAutismAdvocacy.org is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. WashingtonAutismAdvocacy.org may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from January 2013.

**What we collect**  
We may collect the following information:  
• name and job title or specialty  
• contact information including email address  
• demographic information such as how you're connected to autism, zip code, preferences and interests and advocacy needs  
• other information relevant to member surveys and/or advocacy efforts

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  
• Internal record keeping.  
• We may use the information to improve our programs and services.  
• We may periodically send advocacy alerts, newsletters, emails about new programs, servicess or other information which we think you may find of interest and value, using the email address which you have provided.  
• From time to time we may use the information to customize our website according to your interests and needs.

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Sharing**  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties for any purpose, including solicitation of charitable contributions. In rare circumstances, and when required by law, we will notify you that we will be sharing your first name & last initial. Those circumstances include lawsuits initiated by our organization that aim to clarify civil rights protection, insurance and Medicaid benefits.  In such circumstances, you are required to prove you are a member of our organization in order to be included in settlement agreements.

**How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:  
• whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for communicating regional programs and services & advocacy supports.  
• if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct communication purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at Info@WashingtonAutismAdvocacy.org  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties (i.e. training workshops) which we think you may find interesting or helpful if you tell us that you wish this to happen.  
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Info@WashingtonAutismAdvocacy.org.  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

* Get Personalized help.
    ----------------------
    
    Your free membership has many benefits, including access to our parent partners, advocates, training workshops, social groups and more.

* Upcoming Events
    ---------------
    
    December 2024
    
    [
    
    ](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/initial-assessments-evaluations-reevaluations-iees/?occurrence=2024-12-12)
    
    Dec 12 2024
    
    #### [Initial Assessments, evaluations, reevaluations, IEEs](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/initial-assessments-evaluations-reevaluations-iees/?occurrence=2024-12-12)
    
    Zoom https://zoom.us (please download the app and check your internet connectivity)
    
    January 2025
    
    [
    
    ](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/supporting-parents-of-autism-spa-2/?occurrence=2025-01-13)
    
    Jan 13 2025
    
    #### [Supporting Parents of Autism - Friendship Skills for Students Who are High-Masking/Low Support Needs Autistic](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/supporting-parents-of-autism-spa-2/?occurrence=2025-01-13)
    
    Zoom https://zoom.us (please download the app and check your internet connectivity)
    
    [
    
    ](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/best-practices-education-guidelines-for-twice-exceptional-students/?occurrence=2025-01-16)
    
    Jan 16 2025
    
    #### [Best Practices Education Guidelines for Twice Exceptional Students](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/best-practices-education-guidelines-for-twice-exceptional-students/?occurrence=2025-01-16)
    
    Zoom https://zoom.us (please download the app and check your internet connectivity)
    
    March 2025
    
    [
    
    ](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/blueprints-to-special-education-how-to-build-effective-school-services/?occurrence=2025-03-15)
    
    Mar 15 2025
    
    #### [Blueprints to Special Education (How to build effective school services)](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/blueprints-to-special-education-how-to-build-effective-school-services/?occurrence=2025-03-15)
    
    Zoom https://zoom.us (please download the app and check your internet connectivity)
    
    [
    
    ](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/transition-into-adulthood-iep/?occurrence=2025-03-27)
    
    Mar 27 2025
    
    #### [Transition Into Adulthood IEP](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/events/transition-into-adulthood-iep/?occurrence=2025-03-27)
    
    Zoom https://zoom.us (please download the app and check your internet connectivity)
    
    No event found!
    
* Blog Archives
    -------------

Search for:  

#### ABOUT WAA

#### SERVICES & RESOURCES

#### TAKE ACTION  

SIGN UP FOR NEWS AND EVENTS
===========================

Subscription Form - Vertical layout  

First Name

Last Name

Email

SEND ME UPDATES

[

](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/)

721 4th Ave. #891  
Kirkland, WA 98033

#### LATEST POSTS

* [Staff Spotlight: Lizz Carson, Community Engagement Coordinator](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/staff-spotlight-lizz-carson-community-engagement-coordinator/ "Staff Spotlight: Lizz Carson, Community Engagement Coordinator")
* [New Federal Guidance on Functional Behavioral Assessments (FBAs) and Behavioral Intervention Plans (BIPs)](https://washingtonautismalliance.org/new-federal-guidance-on-functional-behavioral-assessments-fbas-and-behavioral-intervention-plans-bips/ "New Federal Guidance on Functional Behavioral Assessments (FBAs) and Behavioral Intervention Plans (BIPs)")

#### QUICK LINKS

Copyright © 2020-2024 All Rights Reserved  
Washington Autism Alliance & Advocacy

Newsletter Form  

### Subscribe to our newsletter

Sign up in the newsletter form below to receive the latest news and updates from WAAA.

* * *

First Name

Last Name

Email

Subscribe

Newsletter Form (#22)  

### Subscribe to our newsletter.

Sign up to receive the latest news and events from WAA.

* * *

First Name

Last Name

Email

SEND ME UPDATES

searchclosearrow-upphoneenvelopephonemap-markercross linkedin facebook pinterest youtube rss twitter instagram facebook-blank rss-blank linkedin-blank pinterest youtube twitter instagram
